[
    {
        "problem": "C02",
        "problem_name": "Write a program to count the Vowels",
        "problem_url": "https://bits.acicts.lk/task/200",
        "solution": "./C02/index.html",
        "source": "https://github.com/Infroid-Coder/BITS-25-Submissions/tree/main/C02"
    },
    {
        "problem": "D10",
        "problem_name": "Design a book mark",
        "problem_url": "https://bits.acicts.lk/task/1000",
        "solution": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/12tKzdHAXhwRTuKZ3CZ-7CEmA2nN65Xg8/view?usp=sharing",
        "source": "https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1HEkA8QuGHyb2GxXFEPsEw2aDFbw3TwOQ?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "problem": "C04",
        "problem_name": "Build a Temperature Converter",
        "problem_url": "https://bits.acicts.lk/task/400",
        "solution": "./C04/index.html",
        "source": "https://github.com/Infroid-Coder/BITS-25-Submissions/tree/main/C04"
    },
    {
        "problem": "D09",
        "problem_name": "Create a logo for an automobile company",
        "problem_url": "https://bits.acicts.lk/task/900",
        "solution": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/16yDnd05k2HnfOw0ZCxJ_mg45KKuWomL5/view?usp=sharing",
        "source": "https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1T5uiOtQSR6GxGHg5BXlmrfHrD2DqQ8ZS?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "problem": "D06",
        "problem_name": "Create a loading Screen for a Game",
        "problem_url": "https://bits.acicts.lk/task/600",
        "solution": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1RjZLpdGzsfXI_UM2VpjVm-uZ8BxCr1jt/view?usp=sharing",
        "source": "https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/136HB2WwbqYjkuNGpY3PJiFGObzvjnfto?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "problem": "C18",
        "problem_name": "Basic Calculator",
        "problem_url": "https://bits.acicts.lk/task/1800",
        "solution": "./C18/index.html",
        "source": "https://github.com/Infroid-Coder/BITS-25-Submissions/tree/main/C18"
    },
    {
        "problem": "C17",
        "problem_name": "Random Quote Generator",
        "problem_url": "https://bits.acicts.lk/task/1700",
        "solution": "./C17/index.html",
        "source": "https://github.com/Infroid-Coder/BITS-25-Submissions/tree/main/C17"
    },
    {
        "problem": "C03",
        "problem_name": "Design a personal portfolio web page",
        "problem_url": "https://bits.acicts.lk/task/300",
        "solution": "./C03/index.html",
        "source": "https://github.com/Infroid-Coder/BITS-25-Submissions/tree/main/C03"
    },
    {
        "problem": "D24",
        "problem_name": "Business Card Design",
        "problem_url": "https://bits.acicts.lk/task/2400",
        "solution": "https://drive.google.com/file/d/1QyF-4MDbp2V0A3ARdKYBaa7gxtVef0BB/view?usp=sharing",
        "source": "https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1RJSWg935up-GkQael8Ui07g7hGaEBFyx?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "problem": "C05",
        "problem_name": "Create a Daily To-Do List Web App",
        "problem_url": "https://bits.acicts.lk/task/500",
        "solution": "./C05/index.html",
        "source": "https://github.com/Infroid-Coder/BITS-25-Submissions/tree/main/C05"
    },
    {
        "problem": "C19",
        "problem_name": "Restaurant Menu Page",
        "problem_url": "https://bits.acicts.lk/task/1900",
        "solution": "./C19/index.html",
        "source": "https://github.com/Infroid-Coder/BITS-25-Submissions/tree/main/C19"
    },
    {
        "problem": "C01",
        "problem_name": "Create a simple rock paper scissor game",
        "problem_url": "https://bits.acicts.lk/task/100",
        "solution": "./C01/index.html",
        "source": "https://github.com/Infroid-Coder/BITS-25-Submissions/tree/main/C01"
    },
    {
        "problem": "C20",
        "problem_name": "Typing Speed Tester",
        "problem_url": "https://bits.acicts.lk/task/2000",
        "solution": "./C20/index.html",
        "source": "https://github.com/Infroid-Coder/BITS-25-Submissions/tree/main/C20"
    },
    {
        "problem": "C31",
        "problem_name": "Palindrome Checker",
        "problem_url": "https://bits.acicts.lk/task/3100",
        "solution": "./C31/index.html",
        "source": "https://github.com/Infroid-Coder/BITS-25-Submissions/tree/main/C31"
    }
]
